what's going on what has
qué es lo que pasa qué es lo que ha
Loli said
dicho Loli
now more
ahora más
Oh the
Ah
same but not to me to you while they
igual pero no a m a tien mientras ellos
live bitter And unhinged you live
viven amargados Y desquiciados tú vives
your life a kiss Maria Jesus but all
tu vida un beso María Jesús pero todo
this that you're seeing all this that I
esto que estáis viendo todo esto lo que
just showed you is an example
os acabo de enseñar es un ejemplo
surely There will be more if you get in to me she
seguramente Habrá más si te metes a mí
sends it to me Karime sends it to me
me lo manda Karime me lo manda algunas
sometimes so that I can put it
veces tal para que yo lo vaya metiendo
in the folders it's not something that if
en las carpetitas no es una cosa que si
I had to be aware of it I don't
yo tuviera que estar pendiente de eso no
do all the content that and everything I
hago todo el contenido que y todo lo que
do in life but you guys noticed
hago en la vida pero ustedes fijaron
while the days go by or rather
mientras que van pasando los días o sea
while the day is going by all
mientras que está pasando el día todas
the things that are between them not
las cosas que están entre ellos no
moving
moviéndose
and it's that they are are are are cloth not family it's not
e es que son son son son tela no familia
cloth I mean between them getting together
no es tela o sea entre ellos juntándose
the conversations this is public
las conversaciones esto es público
imagine the conversations that
imagínate las conversaciones que tendrán
the groups will have that they will have among themselves eh
los grupos que harán entre ellos eh
When the lady came out the other day, this
Cuando salió el otro día la señora esta
Marianela, the Case of the prosecutor saying
la marianela la Case de fiscal diciendo
that they contacted each other to
que entre ellos se contactaban para
organize a joint complaint to
organizar una denuncia conjunta a
YouTube and me Estela and I and they see it as normal they
YouTube y yo Estela y yo y lo ven normal
see it as healthy they see it as healthy eh  I mean but
lo ven sano lo ven sano eh o sea pero
this is all your day to day and we
esto es todo su día a día y nosotros
are here Okay chill now let's
estamos aquí Bueno chill ahora vamos a
see about Loli about Loli Ah I
ver lo de la Loli lo de la Loli Ah Se me
forgot about Lolly you want to Browse the
olvidaba lo de la Lolly quieres Navegar
internet safely and also
de forma segura en internet y además
access all the content of your
acceder a todo el contenido de tus
favorite platforms like Netflix hbo
plataformas favoritas como Netflix hbo
Max or Disney Plus Cyber ​​Ghost VPN And I do
Max o Disney Plus Cyber Ghost VPN Y es
n't know if you know but there is
que no sé si lo sabes pero hay
content that is not available in your country
contenidos que en tu país no están
and with this little trick you can
disponibles y con este truquillo puedes
access all the content wherever you
acceder a todo el contenido estés donde
are I don't know if you know what a VPN is
estés no sé si sabes lo que es una VPN
but it is an extension that you put on your
pero es una extensión que le pones a tu
internet with which it masks the IP and
internet con la que enmascara la IP y
apart from Browse completely safely and
aparte de Navegar completamente seguro y
anonymously without anyone being able to know who you
anónimo sin que nadie pueda saber quién
are and where you are It helps you access
eres y dónde estás Te sirve para acceder
some content that is
a algunos contenidos que están
blocked in your country there are movies and
bloqueados en tu país hay películas y
series on your favorite platforms that
series en tus plataformas favoritas que
are not available there are
no están disponibles hay programas de
television programs for example on mediaset
televisión por ejemplo en mediaset
content that if you try to watch them outside
contenidos que si los intentas ver fuera
of Spain they have a geoblock that does not
de España tienen un geobloqueo que no te
allow you Well with Cyber ​​Ghost VPN that is
lo permite Pues con Cyber Ghost VPN eso
over apart from being protected
se acabó aparte de estar protegido
browsing anonymously you will be able to
navegando bajo el anonimato podrás
access content from all over the
acceder a los contenidos de todo el
planet you will also have Total privacy
planeta además tendrás privacidad Total
since it keeps your connection in  private and
ya que mantiene tu conexión en privado y
protect your data ultra-fast speed
protege tus datos velocidad ultrarápida
to eliminate the lake in any
para eliminar el lago en cualquier juego
online game with which you can enjoy
online con los que podrás disfrutar de
live broadcasts without interruptions and as I have already
directos sin interrupciones y como ya os
told you Freedom to access all the
he dicho Libertad para acceder a todo el
content on the planet wherever and whenever
contenido del planeta dónde y cuando
you want also take advantage of all 8 3%
quieras además aprovecha tod 8 3% de
discount using the link that I
descuento utilizando el enlace que te
leave you in the description of this video and be careful
dejo en la descripción de este vídeo y
because you can try cyberghost VPN
ojo porque puedes probar cyberghost VPN
45 days without obligation and if you are not
45 días sin compromiso y si no te
convinced, ask for a refund and they
convence pides el reembolso y te
will give you your belly back So don't wait
devuelven la panza Así que no esperes
any longer to protect your connection and increase
más para proteger tu conexión y aumentar
your internet experience run and
tu experiencia en internet corre yle
click on the link in the description and take
click al enlace de la descripción y
advantage of this super offer cyberghost
aprovecha esta superoferta cyberghost
VPN to browse completely free and
VPN para navegar completamente libre y
secure we continue with the video why
seguro seguimos con el vídeo por qué
this has been Loli today sent us a tweet
esto ha sido Loli hoy nos puso un tweet
or rather Loli who follows me on Twitter you
o sea Loli que me sigue en Twitter lo
see he follows me he sent us a tweet says
veis me sigue nos puso un tweet dice el
Mr. Javier olit beira describes himself
Señor Javier olit beira se describe el
without realizing it he is one of the
solo sin darse cuenta es uno de los
stalkers that are seen on these networks up to
acosadores que se ven por estas redes
here the one from Troy attacks my father
hasta aquí al de Troya ataca a mi padre
in the worst way and follows me and starts
de la peor forma y me sigue y se pone a
retweeting dalis veir This is
retuitear a dalis veir Es que esto es
tremendous be that  this doesn't even make
tremendo sea que esto no tiene ni
sense anymore but that prosecutor Marianela
sentido ya pero esa fiscal la marianela
No man, this doesn't even make
No hombre es que esto no tiene ya ni
sense anymore no family, this happens every
sentido no familia es que esto ya todos
day, no, as you say, you are already
los días no ual como dice usted ya está
very well informed, there are people who
muy bien informada hay gente que le
like young girls, you bastard of your
gustan las jovencitas desgraciada de tu
[ __ ] life, eh, I have everything
[__] vida eh que yo tengo todo lo que
you've said and you come to do it,
usted ha dicho y viene usted a hacerte
come on, go to hell, be
venga vayase usted a la [__] [__]
careful with Leira, he's a criminal, eh, what did he
cuidado con leira es un delincuente eh
say? He didn't stop breaking some
que ha dicho no se qued de romper unas
CFAs, okay, go to hell
cfas vale váyase usted a la [__] [__]
and don't let the one who said it come out to
y aquí que no salga el que ha dicho a
say what he said,
decir lo que ha dicho a
because this one doesn't eliminate himself, lady,
porque este no se elimina señora
buy yourself a life, change your life, get away
cómprese una vida cambie de vida váyase
from
de
that [ __ ] bastard, kiss Toni,
ese [__] desgraciado que beso Toni
gorgeous, it must be said that this liquor
guapísima hay que decir que este orujo
that this lady consumes is powerful, eh, it is
que consume esta señora es potente eh es
powerful, it is not, this is one of those
potente no es este es un lujo de esos
Galician luxuries made in a village
Gallegos hecho en una allí una una aldea
there and I, it's that this lady
allí de y yo es que es que esta señora
is like this in her house yelling at the
está así en su casa gritándole a la
camera, eh, it's that you, of course, we
cámara eh es que ustedes claro nosotros
have already normalized this, it's not like
ya esto lo hemos normalizado no como que
we react, it's really good  Come on, see what she
reaccionamos lo mmo bueno venga ve que
said about me today, but this lady.
ha dicho hoy de mí pero esta señora
Well, they take this lady seriously.
Bueno a esta señora la toman en serio
Everyone who is joining, not in that
Todos los que se están uniendo no en ese
group that they are creating to hate
grupo que están haciendo de odio contra
me, and they take her seriously as part of their
mí y la toman en serio como parte de su
team in Coruña.
equipo de la Coruña
Hey, careful, hey, these are not jokes. Hey, the internet
eh cuidado eh no son bromas eh internet
is supporting the young women in the
está apoyándose a las mujercitas en los
bars, change your life and make a life for yourself.
bares cámbiese la vida y hágase una vida
This fits with what we have said
algo esto encaja con lo que hemos dicho
many times that she projects her life
muchas veces que ella proyecta su vida
onto others. Now she is talking about
hacia los demás ahora está hablando de
one. She is talking, I think, about
una está hablando creo que es de de de
Joana Morillas who says that her husband
Joana morillas que dice que su marido le
likes young girls and goes for
gusta las jovencitas y se va por Ah de
prostitutes. She is projecting what is
prostitutas está proyectando lo que le
happening to
pasa a
her, we have seen this many times
ella eso lo hemos visto ya muchas veces
and this evidence is already refutable. Hey, better
y son pruebas ya refutables eh mejor
off, unfortunate journalist, come less,
vale desgraciada periodista venida menos
man, man, man, man, now it's okay with me, well or not.
tío tío tío tío ahora me vale bien o no
Because now what
Porque ahora no va a salir por aquí lo
I don't want to be revealed is not going to be revealed here,
que yo no quiero que se
and this one is not going to be private. This one is going because
y este no va a privado este va porque
you might have to put up with it
usted igual se la tiene que aguantar
while they screw
mientras se la meten a
someone else, but not you. I came for the
otra pero no a a tien vine por la
kids and I stayed for  the lordship
chavalería y me quedé por la señoría
face rolling around with a kiss Toni How
cara revolviéndose de beso Toni Cómo
are you son Thank you very much man then
estás hijo Muchísimas gracias tío luego
we'll go to the salsería too for a
nos iremos a la salsería también un
while I have to record a video for the
ratte tengo que grabar un vídeo para el
main channel eh I already have a script here
principal eh tengo aquí ya un guion para
for the main channel I have to record
para el canal principal tengo que grabar
a video I haven't finished the
un vídeo no he terminado el blog de
New York blog yet or rather the Blog thing
Nueva York todavía o sea lo del Blog me
is costing me my life because I have to
está costando la vida porque tengo que
narrate you know says Eva from Avilés has
narrando sabes dice Eva el de Avilés ha
said several things about your box let's see I'm going to
dicho varias cosas de tu caja a ver voy
watch it at
a verlo minuto
such a minute I'm just that what freaks me out is that
tal Yo es que lo que flipo es que la
people are in the mood for nonsense eh Let's see
gente tenga ganas de tontería eh A ver
leave me for a second because it's silent here they are
dejarme un segundo que silencia aquí son
eager for me to go and make a video
ganas de que coja y le haga un vídeo
now and put him back in his place and
ahora y le ponga otra vez en su sitio y
then have him crying for two years eh he
luego lo tenga dos años llorando eh se
starts saying what a pity what
pone a decir que qu pocrí que queé
hypocrisy that they criticized him for the
hipocresía que a él lo criticaron por el
issue of the doll and the Bouquet and what
tema de la muñeca y del Ramo y que qué
hypocrisy that now there are people putting up
hipocresía que ahora haya gente poniendo
a bank account the problem is not
una cuenta del banco el problema no es
the doll and the bouquet The problem is that
la muñeca y el ramo El problema es que
you criticized people for
tú criticaba a la gente de que se
putting up a visa that  they put a
pusieran un visum de que se pusieran
member and you've been doing each thing
miembro y tú has ido haciendo cada cosa
that I criticized the others already have an
que le criticaba a los demás ya tiene
issue with the pantojas no no no no
tema con lo de los pantojas no no no no
but what is it desire that I
ya pero que es ganas de que de que le
do it that I open a live tomorrow and that I
haga de que le abra mañana un directo y
put him in his place again and
de que le ponga en su sitio otra vez y
then Start crying Oh they do
luego se Pon a llorar Ay es que me hacen
a live because if you look for yourself you're going to
un directo cállate porque si te buscas
find yourself Of course of course but but
te vas a encontrar Claro claro per pero
the thing is that also the thing is why does that
es que además la cosa es que por qué ese
guy always know everything we do if I
tío siempre sabe todo lo que hacemos si
'm traveling if I'm on vacation he
estoy de viaje si estoy de vacaciones lo
knows it or rather while when I came back from
sabe o sea mientras que cuando volví de
vacation they sent me click of him
vacaciones me mandaron click de él
saying Yes because I don't know who isn't there
diciendo Sí porque no sé quién no está
because no dude dude Stop seeing me dude he
porque no tío tío Ya deja de verme tío
knows everything he knows everything if tomorrow I
sabe todo sabe todo si mañana yo
have a debate with I don't know who he puts
tengo un debate con no sé quién él pone
one and the worst thing is that he manifests it that is not to say that He
un y lo peor es que lo manifiesta que no
enjoys my content and
es decir que Disfruta de mi contenido y
at least he keeps quiet about it so that
por lo menos se lo calla para que la
people don't notice no no no the worst thing
gente no se dé cuenta no no no lo peor
is that it escapes him and he manifests it
es que se le escapa y lo manifiesta
then when he answers you come the
luego cuando te conteste vienen los
cries three-quarter journalist
lloros periodista del tres al cuarto
bringa complainant of complainant of what Of
bringa denunciante de denunciante de qué
course he's going to put a Blue box everything
Claro que va a poner una caja Blue todo
that  he says and everything he points out
lo que él dice y todo lo que él señala
because who wants to do it, harasser,
porque qul lo quiere hacer acosadora
abuser, useless wretch,
maltratadora inútil desgraciada
okay, she has to be notified of all this, she has to be
vale de todo esto tiene que está ya
held accountable in
notificada tiene que rendir cuentas en
court, eh remember, eh that
un juzgado eh acordaros eh que lo ha
Joana has told it, this is already happening, of course, Val
contado Joana ya pasa claro esto Val
lentico since yes, what happens is that I don't
lentico ya que le Sí lo que pasa que no
know, person in court, this is
sé persona en el juzgado que esta es
another one, they are overwhelming everyone with
otra están agobiando a todo el mundo con
lawsuits and things, but then when they
demandas y cosas pero luego ellos cuando
are sued, don't see, to sit them in
son demandados no veas para sentarlos en
court, then when you
el juzgado luego ellos cuando los
sue them, don't see, so that they come
demandas no veas para que vayan le
down on you, they will all fall on you in a battery and
caigan Le caerán todas en batería y
now go if you and put a tweet
ahora vaya si usted y ponga un tweet
where you say, my sea, I'm jealous because my
donde diga mi mar estoy celosa porque mi
husband wanted to screw her, go away
marido se la quería chinar váyase usted
and talk about yours, you [ __ ] wretch,
y hable de los suyos [__] desgraciada
of course, let's see all these people who
claro vamos a ver toda esta gente que
are super outraged because
está super indignada porque
I put a couple of people in their place
yo puse en su sitio a un par de personas
5 years ago, all these people who are
hace 5 años toda esta gente que está
super outraged with my vocabulary at the
super indignada con mi vocabulario a la
same time, be it Tania, be it the one from Asturias,
vez ya sea Tania ya sea el de asturia ya
not everyone, everyone gets together with this lady,
todos no todos se juntan con esta señora
everyone gets together with this lady, they
todos se juntan con esta señora las
invite them  to their live shows And then
invitan a sus directos Y entonces por
why do you relate to this person no
qué os relacioná con esta persona no
box for Kikos no the Kikos are given to them be
caja para Kikos no los Kikos se los dan
careful that Oliveira said that she
cuidado que oliveira ha dicho que
would break someone's glasses eh it's a
rompería las gafas de alguien eh es un
terrible crime She is being criticized eh
delito terrible Se lo está criticando eh
my goodness but it's
madre mía pero es que es
true someone is calling her to slow her down a
verdad alguien le llama para frenarla un
little no And she said but it's true it's
poco no Y ella di pero es que es verdad
true that Joana's husband
es verdad el que que el marido de Joana
[ __ ] a lot of minors that's what
se [__] un montón de menores eso es lo
you're saying that it's true Loli
que tú estás diciendo que es verdad Loli
and when they sit you in court you
y cuando te sienten en el juzgado
will try to dodge the letter this is it
intentarás esquivar la carta esto es es
is Gila leaving the Mesón de Luis
Es Gila saliendo del Mesón de Luis
Candelas in the Chamberí neighborhood in
Candelas en el barrio de chamberí en
Madrid mother of God coming out with a
Madrid madre de Dios saliendo con una
hangover there that she can't hold back
cogorza ahí que no se puede aguantar
mother of God and here here Tania doesn't come out
madre de Dios y aquí aquí Tania no sale
to do a live show reporting This
a hacer un directo denunciando Esto no
is no no no I don't give a damn that I throw away this
es no no a mí me la suda que me tire el
channel the other one and the one on the motorcycle that I don't give a damn that I get it that I get it in
canal este el otro y el de la moto que
[ __ ] that I sink it in the mud well
[__] que la hundo en el fango pues
Johana goes with her with everything and she will win What
Johana va con ella con todo y la ganará
happens is that  justice is
Lo que pasa que la justicia es
very slow very slow Of course because she's a
lentísima lentísima Claro porque es una
starving woman that's what she's looking for she's a
muerta de hambre es lo que busca es una
starving [ __ ] they don't want her
[__] muerta de hamb que no la quieren en
anywhere I
ninguna parte no
can't oh my god I can't I can't I can't that I've
puedo madre mía que no puedo que no
seen her live the
puedo que que que he visto su directo el
live that I have downloaded and And it's that you ca
directo que tengo descargado y Y es que
n't say anything else about a
no se puede decir otra otra cosa de un
being like that it's that worm that
ser semejante es el gusano ese que se
eats people oh my god then what I can't I
come a la gente madre mía entonces que
can't say anything else
que no puedo que no puedo decir otra
what is Pilar says She has good
cosa que es dice Pilar Tiene buenos
lawyers whatever she wants this guy to take her
abogados cu quiera que la lleve el señor
when the trial is on trial that friend that one that one that
este cuando tenga el juicio amigo ese
spy over there eh
ese eso ese espj que hay ahí eh
Because what's she going to hit me? Uh
Porque qué me va a pegar Uh van a tener
the authorities are going to have to come but the
que acudir las autoridades pero las
real ones because what
reales porque lo que ha sado de mentira
this lady has been lying about is to get her
esta señora por la boca es para cogerla
by the pegs and watch out Oliveira said I do
de los pegas y ojo que oliveira ha dicho
n't know what about breaking some glasses and this
no sé qué de romper unas gafas y esta
lady is believing it by logic because
señora se lo está fe por lógica porque
Oliveira bad bad bad bad bad [ __ ]
oliveira malo malo malo malo malo caca
[ __ ] that's what I say Hey all these people who
caca eso digo yo Oye todos estos que me
are telling me about the glasses like it's
están diciendo lo de las gafas como como
serious wow This isn't the first time
que grave amos Esto no es la primera vez
Loli has done it eh People have already threatened  like that
que lo hace la Loli eh Ya amenazado
eh I was already threatening people like that
gente así eh Ya amenazaba gente así
calmly
tranquilamente
eh men throw this lady through the mouth it's
eh men tira esta señora por la boca es
to catch her by the pegs and watch out that
para cogerla de los pegas y ojo que
Oliveira said I don't know what about breaking
oliveira ha dicho no sé qué de romper
some glasses and this lady is doing it
unas gafas y esta señora se lo está fe
by logic because Oliveira bad bad bad bad bad
por lógica porque oliveira malo malo
poop poop This is not said
malo malo malo caca caca Esto no se dice
this is not done Javi a real bun and
esto no se hace Javi un moño real y
put and stick her head in the same
poner y meterle la cabeza por el mismo
[ __ ] that gave birth to her because she is a [ __ ]
[__] que la parió porque es una [__]
wretch my mother aut Game Over she
desgraciada madre mía aut Game Over ella
cooks it she eats it I'm not going to
se lo guisa ella se lo come no lo voy a
cut it I'm going to continue I already told her what I
cortar voy a seguir le ya le he dicho lo
have to say as I find her I caught her I
que tengo que decir como yo me la
think when she had a drink she
encuentro la pille creo que cuando se le
deleted this eh These are
pasó la papa esto lo borró eh Estos son
the cuts that the Indian put up a
losos cortes que que puso el indio ya
while ago Eh they're not from
hace unos un tiempo Eh no son de ahora
a few weeks ago I think or I don't know let's go to that one to
unas semanas creo o no lo sé vamos a ese
the devil but I'm tracking her but I'm
a la cojo demoño pero la rastreo pero
tracking her well dude they are clearly threats
bien rastrea tío son amenazas claramente
Fito who hab said he's going to break the
Fito que hab ha dicho que va a romper la
dude they are clearly threats on YouTube
tío son amenazas claramente en YouTube
eh And none have come out to post these
eh Y no han salido ninguno a poner estos
click eh Can you send me these click
click eh Me podéis mandar estos click
Lili please  to tweet But this
Lili porfa para para twitear Pero esto
is recent Yes yes of course this is recent
es reciente Sí sí claro esto es reciente
this is now we are seeing it now he
esto es ahora lo estamos viendo ahora
is threatening if he finds I do
está amenazando con si se encuentra a la
n't know if it's La Johana or Jordi because he does
no sé si a La Johana o al Jordi porque
n't understand it either, fine that I know he is
tampoco que se la entienda fina que se
going to drag her and he is going to stick his
que la va arrastrar y le va a meter la
head in the same [ __ ] or I mean it's
cabeza con el mismo [__] o sea es
tremendous it's that no one comes out eh No
tremendo es Es que no sale ninguno eh No
one comes out to say anything about this they are
sale ninguno a decir nada de esto están
here waiting for if I say that I am going to
aquí pendient de que si yo digo que voy
make a box I don't know what I don't know how much
a hacer una caja no sé qué no sé cuánto
but they don't say anything about this those believe the
pero de esto no dicen nada esos cre los
Indian has this I believe the
tiene el indio esto cre lo ha puesto el
Indian put it I didn't realize mother of God
indio no me he dado cuenta madre de Dios
and they are commenting that if I told him
y están comentando que si yo le dije
broom hair I don't know who in 2019 Ah
pelo escoba no sé quién en el 2019 Ah
this This is from summer This is not from
esto Esto es de verano Esto no es de
now Ah that is not from now it is
ahora Ah que no es de ahora que es de
summer a kiss Nani bye talk about your
verano un beso Nani chao hable de su
[ __ ] mother that leaves mine to talk about
[__] madre que deja la mía que hable de
your [ __ ] mother if it is that the acquaintance is going to
su [__] madre si es que la conocido va a
report this this is But what the [ __ ] is
denunciar esta esta es Pero qué [__]
this going This is going to do what
de [__] Esto va Esto va a hacer qué
but if there is nothing more despicable if not
pero si no hay cosa más rastrera si ni
the worm that that that eats
el gusano que que que que se come a los
animals is worse than this but
animales es es peor que esto pero
you understand that you can get away
vosotros entendéis que se puede salir
with a pedal of these characteristics
con un pedal de estas características
this is one has had much worse eh can it
este es uno ha tenido muy peores eh se
go out like that in a live my goodness
puede salir así en un directo madre mía
eh can it [ __ ] it is that they are threats it is that they
eh se puede [__] es que son amenazas es
are huge threats eh It is not possible to
que son amenazas tochas eh No se puede
say that he deleted that live that is a
es decir que borró ese directo eso es un
crime but a crime that is why he
delito pero un delito por eso la
reported her when she complains Well He continues with
denunció cuando se queja Bueno Sigue con
Javi there until he massacres of course and on top of that he does
Javi ahí hasta masacrar claro y encima
not show up Hello what days that well it does not
no se presenta Hola qu días eso pues
appear here this one I do not put it in private
aquí no sale este no lo pongo en privado
this I tell you ag he deleted it he deleted this one I do
este te digo ag lo borró lo borró este
not put it deleted No this one I delete it
no lo pongo borrado No este lo borro sea
but these clips of this lady or I mean I
pero estos clip de esta señora o sea yo
freak out we do not finish seeing all the
flipo no acabamos de ver toda la
indignation that they have not all of them
indignación que tienen no todos los
all of them that chase me
todos los los que me persiguen durante
throughout the [ __ ] day all the
todo el [__] día toda la indignación
tremendous indignation that they have no and it's like and this
tremenda que tienen no y es como y esto
look at you that this one in particular does not
fíjate tú que este este en concreto no
sound to me like I have seen it This is not
me suena a mí haberlo visto Esto no es
undignified all the channels that react
indigna todos los canales que reaccionan
to CP of mine because I said I don't know what
a CP mío porque he dicho no sé qué
Because I posted a thread and this  He said that
Porque he puesto un hilo y esto Dijo que
Johana's act of consideration was
el acto de consideración de Johana era
to get money out of him, my goodness, my goodness,
para sacarle dinero madre mía madre mía
a little less and you play a
un poquito menos y te hagas tú un
little comforter, the finger, the
poquito de consolador el dedito el
finger and if not, what do you think of a
dedito y si no que te parece un chulo
feminist pimp, eh, women too, ar Troya,
feminista eh la mujer también ar Troya
calm down, don't care what they say Yes
me tranquila pasa de lo que digan Sí
man, ar de Troya,
hombre ar de
de Troya, my goodness, de Troya,
Troya de Troya madre mía de Troya me
calm down, don't care what they say, yes man,
tranquila pasa de lo que dian sí hombre
ard de Troya,
ard de
de Troya yes de Troya is
Troya de Troya si de Troya está en
live, what he clicked on me is
directo eso que me ha pinchado está
clicked, damn, I know he's right Loli, a
pinchado hosti se le la razón Loli un
perfect chroma, but I'm not putting this one
croma perfecto eso pero este no lo pongo
in private, I'm not putting this one in private,
en privado este no lo pongo en privado
says one of the best chroma eh, laugh at
dice uno de los mejores cromas eh ríete
FJ's chroma Okay, let's do
del croma de FJ Bueno pues vamos a hacer
a normal live show, let's react to
un directo normal vamos a reaccionar a
gossips,
cotillas
come on, I think I have one more left, look there we
venga creo que me queda otro mira ahí
have Tania, Tania, brand
tenemos la Tania la Tania marca
Chamorro, a piece of [ __ ], the one who's going to end up,
Chamorro un mojón la que va terminar
well, what does she want to report? Oliva, it was in
bueno que quiere denunciar oliva fue en
November, she's telling me,
noviembre me está diciendo
lilin, it was in November, that's two
lilin fue en noviembre o sea hace dos
days since this and me and no one releases a clip of
días de esto y yo y ninguno saca clip de
this, no, there are no live shows around  Trojan night of the
esto no no hay directos por la noche de
Asturian Pepa and all these people
asturiano de la [__] y toda esta gente
not the Twitter accounts Wilson and
no las cuentas de Twitter el Wilson y
all that denouncing this click super
todo eso denunciando este click super
indignant it seems better to you that I
indignado les parece mejor que yo le
slap Ricky
pegue un guantazo a Ricky
Eddie let's react to Ana gossips
Eddie vamos a reaccionar a Ana cotillas
come on I
venga
think I have another one look there we have
creo que me queda otro mira ahí tenemos
Tania Tania and and mark Chamorro and
la Tania la Tania y y marca Chamorro y
a [ __ ] for you the one who is going to end up
un mojón para ti la que va a terminar
well she wants to sue Javi
bueno que quiere denunciar a Javi
Oliveira he has already said that he has already
oliveira ya lo ha dicho que ya le ha
filed I don't know how many complaints And Javi
puesto no sé cuántas denuncias Y Javi
is already making a box to pay the
está haciendo una caja ya para pagar las
complaints of the wallet because he thinks that it will
denuncias de la monedero porque cree que
be long and complicated
va a ser largo y complicado los pleitos
this lady's lawsuits you are in jail because
de esta señora la cárcel eres tú porque
here we have the box okay family when
aquí tenemos la caja vale familia cuando
we finish with one we start with the other
acabemos con uno empezamos con el otro
2147 we have thanks you are the best
2147 llevamos gracias sois los mejores
Ok I love you very much What is a
Ok os quiero muchísimo La que es una
[ __ ] disgrace you have the link fixed
[__] desgracia tenéis el enlace fijado
there Lili posted it okay in the
ahí lo ha puesto Lili vale en el
chat it is you lady are you a [ __ ]
chat eres tú señora es usted una [__]
disgrace go to sleep this
desgraciada váyase usted a dormir esto
is to Tania no what you are saying
es a la Tania no lo que le está diciendo
here is to Tania no  this was Tania
aquí es a la Tania no esto era la Tania
now don't pay the complaints of the
ahora no pagar las denuncias de la
long and complicated wallet the lawsuits
monedero largo y complicado los pleitos
of this lady the jail is you because
de esta señora la cárcel eres tú porque
the one who is a wretched [ __ ] is you
la que es una [__] desgraciada eres tú
lady you are a wretched [ __ ]
señora es usted una [__] des graciada
go to sleep and and and and
váyase usted a dormir y y y y
charge her with misfortune and human rubble
encárgale desgracia y escombro humano no
you can't be a worse person the mother you
puede ser usted peor persona la madre
have to take care of is yours to
que tiene que cuidar es a la suya a la
Johana eh to the elderly people that
Johana eh a la a la gente mayor que
you may have robbed it must have been
usted puede haber robado debe haber sido
you are telling your life story here on
usted está contando su vida aquí en
YouTube here nobody has robbed any
YouTube aquí nadie a robado a ninguna
elderly person here the only host Joana
persona mayor aquí la única [__] Joana
Do you want me to put the link and you upload
Quieres que te ponga el enlace y subes
here with me host that I am in
aquí con conmigo [__] que estoy en
esar Do you want me to put the link you have
esar Quieres que te ponga el enlace
balls you upload here with me you upload
tienes huevo subes aquí conmigo subes
here and in am morillas you upload here you have
aquí y en am morillas subes aquí tienes
balls you have balls you have ovary you have no
huevos tienes [__] tienes ovario no
ovaries or balls or eggs or
tienes ovarios ni [__] ni huevos ni
dignity or human esses or person I
dignidad ni eses humana ni persona te
put the link for you Johana answer only yes
pongo el enlace Johana contesta solo sí
or no V What a character eh how strong What a
o no V Qué personaje eh qué fuerte Qué
character eh it's hard to find something
personaje eh es difícil encontrar algo
that surpasses this complicated character
que supere a este personaje complicado
how strong the Ne you are at a level of  of
qué ferte la Ne estás un nivel de de
very high tannins eh a
taninos altísimo eh un volumen
brutal alcoholic volume eh in How strong
alcohólico brutal eh en En qué fuerte
man the Tasting not of what you drink is not
tío la Cata no de lo que tomas no está
the host what a [ __ ] man
la [__] qué putada
how strong I have not lost something the
tío qué fuerte no he perdido una cosa la
stone is going to fall on her good Well let's see
tiesta le va a caer una buena Pues a ver
if it's true because not see if it's slow
si es verdad porque no ver si es lento
slow slow I don't know how to go to
lento lento yo no sé cómo ir a lo de
Johana's I haven't spoken to her in a
Johana no he hablado con ella hace
while I have to ask her I
tiempo le tengo que preguntar Me
congratulate myself on the rewi she wrote to me to
felicito por el rewi me escribió para
congratulate me on the rewind but she didn't
felicitarme por el rewind pero no le
ask more How is she doing with this
preguntó a más Cómo lleva este
issue but but I'm going to ask her man
tema pero pero le voy a preguntar tío
my goodness eh my goodness the aunt is there
madre mía eh madre mía la tía está ahí
under the bed writing on
debajo de la cama escribiendo por
YouTube while her husband will be in the
YouTube mientras su marido estará en
bars with her he is projecting
la en los bares con la está proyectando
what's happening to her eh
lo que le pasa a ella eh
ladies you are a [ __ ] [ __ ] of your life
señoritas desgraciada de tu [__] vida
You are a [ __ ] of your [ __ ] life
eres Eres una [__] de tu [__] vida
show some proof once of everything that you
enseña unaa prueba una vez de todo lo
have said and what you have done Do you
que lo que has dicho y lo que has hecho
want me to give you the link Joana you have
Quieres que te ponga el enlace Joana
balls you have ovaries you have
tienes huevos tienes ovarios tú tienes
one ovary or two you have my mobile here don't
un ovario o dos tien mi móvil aquí no
write she has my
escribas tiene mi
mobile ringa ringa she has my mobile you have
móvil ringa ringa tiene mi móvil tienes
my  mobile and I you guys are not here this yes we
mi móvil y yo ustedes no está esto sí lo
saw this we saw it Lili wale here dude
vimos esto lo vimos Lili wale aquí tío
How incredibly annoying the one we were
Qué pesado increíble el que decíamos de
joking that he came back in 2020 and it turns out he
broma que volv al 2020 y resulta que si
came back here with all his obsessed
volvió aquí con todos sus obsesionados a
smokers more jpf grandpa Yes, continue
fumas más jpf abuelo Eso sí sigan
supporting grandpa's box and donate your
apoyado la caja del abuelo y donen
honor if you want it I mean you
señoría ustedes si lo quieren O sea tú
come here to ask people to
vienes aquí a pedirle a la gente que
support the box with a where you come you see
apoyen la caja con un dó vienes tú veis
what I have to put up with from
lo que tengo que aguantar por parte de
the kids family do you see it as normal
la chavalería familia lo veis normal
God, well I didn't remember this having
Dios pues yo no recordaba esto haberlo
seen it it's that there are so many things you've already missed me
visto es que son tantas cosas ya me has
you're a guy obsessed
echado de menos eres un tío obsesionado
with me you're dangerous Ah this you're
conmigo eres peligroso Ah esto eres
dangerous he tells me this is to me this is that
peligroso me dice esto es a mí esto es
eh Loli what he's saying is that I
eh Loli lo que está diciendo es que yo
opened the box because I've
he abierto la caja porque la he hecho de
missed her that since she's not
menos a ella que como ella no está en
anyway what can I tell you that since she's not
fin qué os cuento que como ella no está
here anymore then we needed to
aquí ya pues entonces hemos necesitado
open a box because we're
abrir una caja porque estamos
obsessed with her and since she's not
obsesionados con ella y que como ella no
here then the box isn't full that's what he
está aquí pues la caja no se llena eso
's
es lo que está
saying my god for me point of for
diciendo madre mía para mi punto de para
me  and my life you are dangerous you are a
mí y mi vida eres peligroso eses un
parasite in my life You are a
parásito de mi vida en mi vida Eres un
[ __ ] parasite dude Go to court You are a
[__] parásito tío Vete a juzgado Eres un
pimp Go to court you know and he does not
chulo Vete al jugado sabes y no se
appear in the lawsuit that we have filed against him
presenta en la demanda que le hemos
eh what can I tell you family What a shame it
eh qué os digo familia Qué vergüenza no
can not be normalized Javi is bursting that you
se puede normalizar Javi revienta que tú
are above Javi you are bursting that
estás por encima Javi le revientas que
you are above eh mom but that is
tú estés por encima eh mam pero es que
what I am telling you and and and I know I am very
es lo que os digo y y y sé que soy muy
tiresome these last few days but that is
cansino estos últimos días pero es que
what I am telling you eh I would love to
es lo que os digo eh A mí me encantaría
take another lawsuit against this lady and
[__] otra demanda a esta señora y
file another one on her because this is already unpunished
ponerle otra es que esto ya es impune
this is already unpunished Javi leave it like that he
esto ya es impune Javi deja wale si
is an [ __ ] I mean this is already
igual es un capullo o sea esto ya es
unpunished why because we have already
impune por qué porque nosotros ya le
filed a lawsuit the date is set
hemos puesto una demanda la fecha está
for 2026 for the trial the lady has not
para el 2026 del juicio la señora no se
appeared then you will see this lady
ha personado luego verás tú esta señora
to pay the sentence okay Eh already everything she
para pagar la condena vale Eh ya todo lo
says now I can not sue her anymore
que diga ya yo no puedo demandarla más
now I have to take care of the
yo ahora me tengo que hacer cargo del
other special of the other special of the
otro especial de la otra especial del
other that we have also filed a
del otro que le hemos puesto también una
lawsuit against the laser  len I mean of course
demanda el laser len o sea claro es que
people say no but it's that you You
la gente dice no pero es que tú Tú
have money of course man I have
tienes dinero claro hombre yo tengo
money for everyone infinite and little is
dinero para todos infinito y poco se
said about Loli's stepchildren the box is
habla de los hijastros de Loli la caja
going to run dry Santi the box well
se va a quedar seca Santi la caja pues
the box of course the box is going to run
la caja claro la caja se va a quedar
dry in a pl pl the gossip this
seca en un pl pl el salseo de esta
week in x has been you Javi everyone has been
semana en x ha sido tú Javi todos los
waiting for you of the
han estado pendient de ti de las
donations already they are suffering with the
donaciones ya ya están sufriendo con el
issue of the box but because of course the earthquake
tema de la caja pero por que claro el
It's that this the earthquake It's that
temblor Es que esto el temblor Es que
if we achieve the objective it will go to go to
esto si conseguimos el objetivo va a ir
file lawsuits against each and every
para ir poniendo demandas a todos y cada
one of them Javi everything I say
unos ellos Javi está todo lo que diga
now is free of course It's that I can't
ahora es de gratis claro Es que yo ya no
sue everyone anymore no it's that of
puedo demandar más a todos no es que
course it's that you're asking for money and And
claro es que estás pidiendo dinero y Y
you already earn money Yes of course but
tú ya ganas dinero Sí claro pero
Then what do we do I can't get my
Entonces qué hacemos no puedo meterle
hands on all of these no we don't have You are a
mano a todos estos no no tenemos Eres un
pimp of your friends what the [ __ ] eh eh does
chulo de tus amigos qué [__] eh eh
this have to do with everything
tiene esto que ver con con todo la caja
you made the box and I'll tell you one thing I'm
la has hecho y te digo una una cosa Lo
very sorry Mr. Javier Oliveira but
siento mucho señor Javier oliveira pero
you have given a bank account and in
usted ha dado una cuenta bancaria y en
the bank account there is  two digits that
la cuenta bancaria hay dos dígitos que
refer to the population where you
se refieren a la población donde usted
reside trust yourself now where you are going do not
reside fíate tú ya para dónde se va no
close the cash register Sara the cash register the cash register I am not
cierres la caja Sara la caja la caja no
going to close it obviously I am not
la voy a cerrar evidentemente la caja no
going to close it But what I want is for
la voy a cerrar Pero yo lo que quiero es
people to
que la gente
understand the purpose of the cash register What is it I
entienda el destino de la caja Cuál es
am showing you every day to all
os estoy enseñando todos los días a toda
these people what they do and I want
esta gente A qué se dedican y yo quiero
someone to explain to me who has the
que alguien me explique quién tiene
capacity to get their hands on all of
capacidad de poder meterle mano a todos
these because I don't I don't know if people
estos porque yo no yo no sé si la gente
think that I am Ivai or Auron Play or
se piensa que yo soy ivai o auron Play o
one of those but I do not have the
alguno de esos pero yo no tengo
capacity to sue them all the
capacidad para demandarlos a todos la
cash register hurts a lot exactly monce but
caja duele mucho exactamente monce pero
trust yourself what you are saying or rather what you
fíate tú lo que está diciendo o sea lo
are saying is Of course the cash register
que está diciendo es Claro que la caja
that I have put an account number that
que he puesto un número de cuenta que
has two digits that are from the city
tiene dos dígitos que son de la ciudad
where I live I live in Seville do you want me to
donde vivo vivo en Sevilla quieres que
tell you without without telling you the digits I
te lo diga sin sin decirte los dígitos
live in Seville if you show up in
vivo en Sevilla si te personas en el
court you would know my address because it is
juzgado sabrías Mi dirección porquees
Of course my address is presented or are they
Claro mi dirección está presentada o me
going to ask for my ID no when we go to
van a pedir el dni no cuando vayamos a
court but the cash register does not have any
juicio pero en la caja no pone ningún
account number  He understands
número de cuenta se entiende
their problems perfectly,
perfectamente el problemas de ellos
man. Of course they have a problem with the
hombre Claro que tienen un problema con
cash register because he knows what's
lo de la caja porque sabe la que se les
coming to them, he says, Santi, puny, he's not rich.
viene dice Santi canijo no es rico
Even if it seems exactly like that, Santi, one
Aunque lo parezca exactamente Santi una
thing is what I look like. And another is what I
cosa es lo que yo parezca Y otro es lo
am. But what is
que soy Pero qué es lo que está contando
this lady talking about? She's a fool in trouble, eh,
esta señora es un tonto en apuros eh
angry. And obsessed with a
encabritado Y obsesionado con una mujer
52-year-old woman who wants you to leave her alone.
de 52 años que quiere que la dejes en
Man, leave me alone but a Loli, you
paz tío déjame en paz pero un Loli tú me
stop mentioning me and you pay me everything you have to
dejas de mencionar y me pagas todo lo
pay me and you either
que me tienes que pagar y te o te
show up in court or you pay it
presentas en el juzgado o lo pagas
directly and we close the procedure
directamente y cerramos el procedimiento
and I never hear from you again. Of course
y yo no vuelvo a saber más nada de ti
not, you pay me what was
claro que no tú me pagas lo que se te ha
asked of you in the lawsuit and you pay me the things
pedido en la demanda y me pagas las cos
obviously and you don't mention me again and see you
evidentemente y no me mencionas más y
later. I love the cash register, it's priceless to
hasta luego amo la caja no tiene precio
see him rage but not to see what they're up to
verlo rabiar pero no ver la que llevan
with the cash register. They're all with the
liado con la caja están todos Con la
c, my goodness, what they have. eh, moment,
c madre mía la que tienen eh momento os
have you realized that the topic of the day,
habéis dado cuenta que el tema del día
the topic of the week, is that one, it's not over,
el tema de la semana es esa no se acabó
but this lady from  where the [ __ ] did he
pero esta señora de dónde [__] ha
come from, dude How is it possible that there are
salido macho Cómo cómo es posible que
people who swallow this from
que que haya gente que se trague esto de
this woman How is it possible that people do
esta mujer cómo es posible que la gente
n't see the state in which this
no vean en el estado en la que esta
lady is making these statements
señora está haciendo estas declaraciones
How is it possible that those who
cómo es posible que que que los que lo
see it don't tell her or or that they
vean m pues no se lo digan o o que les
go along with it Or how is it possible
sigan la corriente o cómo es posible
Well, it's possible because it's the
bueno pues es posible porque es la
society in which we have to live and
sociedad en la que nos ha tocado vivir y
in the society that we have to live Well, there are
en la sociedad que nos ha tocado vivir
attics, there are ground floors and there are basements
Pues hay esto hay áticos hay bajos y hay
and below the basements
sótanos y por debajo de los sótanos
are the sewers and right now in this
están las cloacas y ahora mismo en esta
society the classes are given a voice I am
sociedad a las clas se les da voz Yo son
things that I am things I am things that I do
cosas que yo son cosas yo son cosas que
n't understand Let's see you go to
no entiendo a ver tú te vas para las
Wilson's accounts What is
cuentas estas de Wilson de qué está
Wilson talking about? Well, Wilson is
hablando Wilson pues Wilson está
waiting for what gas had
pendiente de de que gasa ha tenido hoy
4,500 viewers today and while
4500 espectadores y y de mientras
telesalseo had 2,500 that's your t Wilson
telesalseo tenía 2500 eso es tu t Wilson
that another youtuber is doing well a
que otro youtuber le está yendo bien un
topic seems perfect to me he has
tema a mí me parece perfecto me ha
released me he has released me it seems great to me
soltado me ha soltado me parece de lujo
200 of Troy in the  box Yes yes the
200 de de Troya en la caja Sí sí la
truth is that it coincides with the
verdad es que está coincidenci con la
ard cause of Troy has given 200 has not
causa ard de Troya ha dado 200 no ha
given two of 200 eh to the one from Troy This is
dado dos de 200 eh al de Troya Este es
your tweet Wilson Put me here below too
tu tweet Wilson Ponme también aquí abajo
that there is IV has had more viewers than
que hay IV ha tenid más espectadores que
me Diego Arabal has also had
yo Diego arabal ha tenido hoy también
more viewers today mik Vasco has more
más espectadores mik Vasco tiene más
viewers also put those who have
espectadores pon también los que tienen
less that are
menos que son
more but it's as if as if 2500 were or
más pero es como si como si 2500 fuera o
so this what is it this is your this
sea esto qué es lo que este es tu esto
is your happiness today Wilson this is your your
es tu felicidad hoy Wilson esto es tu tu
twi that al much that the man is doing well
twi que al much que al hombre le va bien
with another topic and he has sado cha kissed his
con otro tema y nos ha sado cha le beso
mouth still happens I hope he has
la boca alún pasa Ojalá tenga todos los
4500 every day not 9000 leaving us
días 4500 no 9000 dejándonos a nosotros
in peace I hope 9000 that he is defending
en paz Ojalá 9000 que está defendiendo
now what he has criticized with me that I
ahora lo que conmigo ha criticado que yo
insulted her in the mother's trial
en el juicio de la madre la he insultado
and he thought it was terrible and now the other
y a él le parecía fatal y ahora al otro
is defending it because it is freedom
lo está defendiendo porque es libertad
of expression But oh well I don't care I'm not
de expresión Pero bueno Me da igual No
going to comment on anything or dedicate
le voy ni a comentar nada ni a dedicar
an excerpt or anything I hope he has  9000
un extracto ni nada ojalá tenga 9000
leaving me alone because I was one of
dejándome a mí en paz porque era de los
yours but this is your tweet 240
vuestros pero que este es tu tweet 240
has given come on The ard of Troy has given
ha dado venga ya El ard de Troya ha dado
240 bucks it doesn't appear to me Hey this just went
240 pavos no me aparece Oye esto acaba
up it didn't just go up now it just went
de subir no acaba de subir ahora acaba
up Someone has donated now let's see
de subir Alguien ha donado ahora a ver
wait Let's keep seeing what he
espérate Vamos a seguir viendo qué es lo
tweets well come on let's you this be your
que twitea pues vamos que tú este sea tu
reason for happiness today I already
motivo de felicidad de hoy yo ya de
really Ah retweet that they want to shut me down they challenge me
verdad Ah retuitea que me quieren cerrar
that they are arguing with me about something
retan que me están discutiendo una cosa
from
del
2022 that has already been fixed it's pending
2022 que ya arregló está pendiente de
Elena de Ortega speaks Ah that Elena Speaks
Elena de Ortega habla Ah que Elena Habla
clearly logical not that they give their opinion no
claro lógico no que opinen no no puede
Elena de Ortega cannot give her opinion on all these
opinar Elena de Ortega de todos estos
issues Look if they noticed the clicks
temas Mira se sea fijaron los clicks
trust you what she has done crazy but this
fíate tú lo que ha hecho loco pero esto
What is it gentlemen has retweeted this has
Qué es señores ha retuiteado esto ha
retweeted I hear a tweet from rpb
retuiteado heo un tweet de rpb
rpb that rpb tweeted yesterday
rpb que rpb ayer tuiteó
defending himself despite the differences we
defendiéndose a pesar de las diferencias
have the guy
que tengamos el tío
tweeted
twite de
defending ourselves March of
defendiéndonos marzo de
2023 retweet this no thief is
2023 a retuitear esto ningún trinque se
safe from their
salva de su
archives I find it disgusting disgusting disgusting disgusting
hemeroteca me parece asqueroso asqueroso
that there are eh
asqueroso asqueroso que que los hay eh
people on networks with a smile on their face
gente en redes con una sonrisa a la cara
making memes and rejoicing over the firing
haciendo memes y alegrándose el despido
of a girl you may like it or
de una chavala te puede caer mejor o
dislike it eh I mean you may like it or
peor eh o sea te puede caer mejor o
dislike it that they started saying that I was here they
peor que se pusieron a decir que yo aquí
cut the clip they cut it
me estaba cortan el clip lo recortan
as always when I was rejoicing
como siempre que yo estaba alegrándome
that Diego had been fired I
de que a Diego lo habían hechado yo no
wasn't laughing at all about it and
me estaba riendo ni mucho menos de eso y
here I think I was even talking to
yo aquí creo que incluso me hablaba con
him look how it's almost two years well
él fíjate tú cómo es casi dos años bueno
no here I was almost two years since the
no aquí tenía yo la casi dos años del
tweet Pili but apart from that this
tweet Pili pero es que aparte que esto
is a manipulation I mean I
es una manipulación O sea yo no me
wasn't rejoicing that here I was talking
estaba alegrando que aquí me hablaba yo
to Diego Arrabal and doing collaborations
con Diego arrabal y hacía colaboraciones
with him This was the irony that they
con él Esto fue la ironía de que lo
removed him and put Marina in or
quitaron a él y pusieron a Marina o
some move like that I don't remember I would have to
alguna movida así no me acuerdo tendría
see the live I think the live
que ver el directo creo que el directo
then we saw the full click and since he
luego vimos el click completo y como él
saw fit today to retweet This
ha tenido a bien hoy retuitear Esto
Pablo Franco, Javi Oliveira's and
Pablo Franco abogado de Javi oliveira y
Dallas' lawyer, joins the crowdfunding to
Dallas se une a los crowdfunding para
cover legal expenses and I have
cubrir gastos judiciales y y todos tengo
a few of the tips here that
aquí unos cuantos de cillas que me ha
Salomé sent me, from a few of them
mandado Salomé de unos cuantos de ellos
asking for money for the trials this
pidiendo dinero para los juicios este
very day. The knife, the one who sued the one
mismo El faca el que ha demandado al el
who sued Pablo has a
que ha demandado a Pablo tiene un tiene
box that I got the idea from him
una caja que la idea la he cogido de él
Javi Oliveira says that he doesn't need to ask for
Javi oliveira dice que no necesita pedir
food but that the box has a
para comer pero que la caja tienen un
mess with the box that if I earn a lot of
jaleo con la caja que si yo gano mucho
money, that if the box that if I don't know what,
dinero que si la caja que si no sé qué
challenging Joh on the news because he gives me
em retando joh en planas porque me pone
a hot dog, it's that I don't understand it, I
un perrito es que yo no lo entiendo o
mean, there are times when they say that I'm poor and that
sea hay veces que dicen que soy pobre y
things are very easy for me, I mean,
que me van las cosas muy o sea aquí
look at you. Here he's rejoicing that
fíjate tú Aquí se está alegrando de que
Gun Pasa has more viewers than me and
gun pasa tiene más espectadores que yo y
I'm down because I have 2,500
yo estoy hundido porque tengo 2500
viewers. The one from Troy said that if he was
espectadores al de Troya dijo que si le
sued for putting up a bar and now Lili I
demandaban por ponía una barra y ya Lili
have clicks from everyone saying the same thing, I
tengo click de todos diciendo lo mismo
have clips from everyone and don't see the
tengo clip de todos y no vean el
suffering they have with the box and don't
sufrimiento que tienen con la caja y no
see the suffering they have with  the
vea el sufrimiento que tienen con la
box what's wrong with you that you go there falling
caja qué os pasa que vais ahí cayendo
one by one with this box you go there falling
uno a uno con esta caja vais ahí cayendo
one by one but why not why don't you
uno a uno pero por qué no por qué no
click from there from Loli
pones click de de ahí de la Loli
threatening people those clicks don't
amenazando a la gente esos click no te
seem to you Comment bles that the
parecen Comenta bles que la ponga el
facua puts it, they don't criticize it no no but it
facua no lo critican no no pero que no
's not the FAO all of them have said if they
es el FAO todos ellos han dicho si me
report me I'll put a bar but if I
denuncian pongo una barra pero si la
put it it's the topic of the week but that's
pongo yo es el tema de la semana pero es
what I'm telling you I mean no no it's that he
que es lo que te digo O sea no no es que
has money Ah I have money to
tiene dinero Ah tengo dinero para
sue them all Ah well [ __ ] where do I have it
demandarlos a todos Ah pues [__] dónde
where is it For everything to ha to
lo tengo dónde está Para todo para ha
sue them all I have money let's
para demandarlos a todos tengo dinero a
see where it is but then I'm
ver dónde está pero luego estoy
ruined I mean I don't understand I don't understand I
arruinado O sea no lo entiendo No lo
'm ruined I'm not
entiendo estoy arruinado no estoy
ruined I'm doing well or I'm doing bad to clarify
arruinado me va bien o me va mal aclarar
or is the world upside down all these
o es el mundo al revés todos estos
fecal waste channels are the world upside
canales de residuos fecales son el mundo
down I mean Authentic harassers eh
al revés o sea Auténticos acosadores eh
using harassment to people who expose
usando de acoso a personas que exponen
their harassment their crimes and their [ __ ] it's
sus acosos sus delitos y sus [__] es
the world upside down totally upside down
el mundo al revés totalmente al revés
this comes a time Javi You
esto llega un momento Javi Tú siempre
are always their topic of the week even when you
eres su tema de la semana hasta cuando
're in  New York when I was in
estás en Nueva York cuando estaba en
New York they weren't taking out and
Nueva York no estaban sacando y
reacting to the clicks of New York
reaccionando a los click de Nueva York
they were reacting to how the
estaban reaccionando a cómo bailaban las
Joker stairs were dancing they were reacting
escaleras del Joker estaban reaccionando
to whether I had more or less clothes on whether I
a si me a si tenía más o menos ropa a si
was more or less fat that's all It's all
estoy más o menos gordo es todo Es todo
the time They have another donor
el tiempo Ellos tienen a otra donadora
that has come out there's another donor now who who
que ha salido hay otra donad ahora quién
is the new donor I don't know her
quién es la nueva donadora no la conozco
moment that already causes you some man no what are you
momento que ya te causa unas tío no que
saying already it's what people say no it's that
dices ya es que dice la gente no es que
yesterday you were commenting like very bad
ayer estabas comentando como muy de mala
mood not like very no no I'm not
[__] no como muy no no ni estoy
nervous nor am I I'm chill I'm fine I
nervioso ni estoy estoy chill estoy bien
mean I'm lucky to be calm
o sea tengo la suerte de estar tranquilo
man I would love to fill the box but
hombre Me encantaría llenar la caja pero
because I would calmly take Pablo and the
porque cogería tranquilísimo a Pablo y
other lawyer and give each one
al otro abogado y a cada uno le daría
their cases you know I would give each one their
sus casos sabes a cada uno le daría sus
cases so that they are all sued
casos para que estén todos demandados
if we fill the box everyone will be
si llenamos la caja todos van a estar
sued everyone and I'm here quietly I'm
demandados todos y yo aquí tranquilito
going to wait for it and then if we win
voy a esperarlo y ya luego si ganamos ya
we'll see what we do okay they suffered
veremos lo que hacemos vale sufrieron
a lot seeing canijo in Times Square but it
mucho viendo canijo en Time Square pero
's not that I'm nervous or
no es ni que yo esté nervioso ni
upset or no it's that man that's what
alterado ni no ya es que es tío es lo
Jordi is saying Yeah  it's that it is it's that
que está diciendo Jordi Ya es que
you wake up in the morning
es ya es que te levantas por la mañana
seven tweets of seven clips from Twitter
siete twits de siete clips de Twitter
thrown away because there's a special person
tirado porque hay una personita especial
or rather when it's not one thing the one who
o sea cuando no es una cosa el que te
makes child pornography with you and threatens to
hace pornografía infantil con y amenaza
rape your children it's another who
con violar a tus hijos es otro que se
spends every day impersonating
dedica todos los días a suplantar la
all the creators to
identidad de todos los creadores para
throw all the tweets from Twitter at you
tirarte todos los tweets de Twitter
when it's not another answering all of
cuando no es otro contestando a todos
them and joining together when you don't
ellos y uniéndose entre ellos cuando no
get a call that they are among
te llega una llamada de que están entre
them making a collective complaint to
ellos haciendo una denuncia colectiva a
YouTube and they start calling each other to
YouTube y se ponen a llamarse a
participate in space with ladies it's that
participar en space con señoras es que
every day that you are terrible it's that it's
todos los días que estáis fatal es que
not healthy really if it's not it's not
no es sano de verdad si es que no no es
neither anger nor it's that it's that it's all Santi
ni enfado ni es que es que es todo Santi
how would you convince people to
tú cómo convencería a la gente para que
fill the box with 1700 people
llenásemos la caja de una 1700 personas
you have here Santi it depends on you right now
tienes aquí Santi depende de ti ahora
Santi the box depends on you right now
mismo Santi la caja depende de ti ahora
already [ __ ] but it's that it's impossible to
mismo ya [__] pero es que es imposible
do anything there is nothing to expose everything you
hacer nada no hay nada que exponer todo
expose is the same everything everything turns around I
lo que expongas es igual todo todo se da
mean in the end Exactly Silvia
la vuelta o sea al final Exacto Silvia
canarionaa says let's see Javi the  that they
canarionaa dice a ver Javi el que
name your son in a bad way He has to
nombren a tu hijo para mal Tiene que
remove anyone from kiso Silvia but it's just that it does
sacar de kiso a cualquiera Silvia pero
n't affect me anymore Silvia It's
es que ya ya no me afecta Silvia Es
sad but it's like that it doesn't
triste pero es que es así ya no me
affect me anymore raed comes out threatening my
afecta ya me sale raed amenazando a mi
son but yes but yes every day Eh
hijo pero si pero si todos los días Eh
when they're not threatening I mean do you remember that
cuando no amenazan o sea os acordáis que
recently an account also came out
hace poco salió también una cuenta
I was here live and I don't know what I
estaba yo aquí en directo y no sé queé
showed from my phone like this and the photo of
enseñé del móvil así y se vio la foto de
my wallpaper was seen which was a
el fondo de pantalla mía que era una
photo of Leo okay And Leo's photo was seen just in passing
foto de Leo vale Y se vio así de refilón
and they created a
la foto de Leo y se crearon una cuenta
Twitter account and all day long they were tweeting
de Twitter y todo el día estaban twite
all day long tweeting Leo's photo in the
todo el día twite la foto de Leo a la
long run it affects you no no no yeah it's not that
larga te afecta no no no si es que no es
you get affected how lazy Look the other
que te afectes que pereza Mira el otro
day they were sending me another account
día me estaban mandando otra cuenta más
from a person who had created an
de una persona que se habría creado una
account just to say that I was
cuenta solamente para decir que yo me
[ __ ] my ass I don't know what guy let's see
follaba la miare que no sé qué tío a ver
if I can find it because I have so many
si lo encuentro que tengo tantos
messages that Lili probably knows what I'm
mensajes que seguro que Lili sabe a lo
talking about dude it was an account that had been
que me refiero tío era una cuenta que se
created exclusively to
había creado exclusivamente para
respond to every tweet from you know what  how
responder a cada tweet de sabes es como
I don't know anyway here the cowards always win
no sé yo en fin aquí ganan siempre los
the cowards always win right
cobardes siempre ganan los cobardes no
Okay but okay had a bad day today
Bueno pero bueno tenido un mal día hoy
I saw it like that no good This
yo lo he visto Así no bueno Esto
continues saying
continúa diciendo
[ __ ] Diego Arabal has been heavily
gilipollez Diego arabal ha sido muy
criticized for this headline breaking news
criticado por este titular última hora
dies at 88 in the hospital
muere a los 88 años en el hospital
damn God iñaki urruti
hostias Dios iñaki urruti
I hope you go to the
espero que vayas o al
optician or get your head fixed one
oculista o que te arreglen la cabeza una
of the two things because he says iñaki
de las dos cosas porque dice iñaki
urruti says Let's see yesterday you were playing with the
urruti dice A ver tú ayer jugabas con la
death of Julio Iglesias with the death
muerte de Julio Iglesias con la muerte
of Julio Iglesias your mother
de Julio Iglesias habrá jugado tu madre
or your father must have played I haven't played with the death
o tu padre yo no he jugado con la muerte
of Julio Iglesias How come I have played with
de Julio Iglesias Cómo que he jugado con
the death of Julio
la muerte de Julio
Iglesias When
Iglesias Cuándo
where does he get angry no oh it's closed Ah okay you ca
dónde se enfada no ay es cerrado Ah vale
n't read no I'm looking to
que no sabes leer no Estoy buscando a
see what it says in Yellow no what
ver qué es lo que pone en Amarillo no
is the justification no in Yellow
que es la justificación no en Amarillo
here in small it says this Saturday
aquí en pequeño pone este sábado 11 de
January 11th at 5 the priest
enero a las 5 falleció el sacerdote
journalist and businessman Luis del esema passed away
periodista y empresario Luis del esema
Ah what is this one here on the corner
Ah que es este de aquí de la esquina
well each one I'm that about this man
bueno cada uno Yo es que de este hombre
No comment each one that  do what he sees
No comenta cada uno que haga lo que vea
and let him carry things as he sees fit.
y que lleve las cosas como él vea no